{
  "questions": {
    "specificAnswerQuestions": [
      {
        "question": "1",
        "info": "Who was the legendary Benedictine monk who invented champagne?",
        "Answer": "Dom Perignon"
      },
      {
        "question": "2",
        "info": "Name the largest freshwater lake in the world.",
        "Answer": "Lake Superior"
      },
      {
        "question": "3",
        "info": "Where would you find the Sea of Tranquility?",
        "Answer": "The Moon"
      },
      {
        "question": "4",
        "info": "What is someone who shoes horses called?",
        "Answer": "A farrier"
      },
      {
        "question": "5",
        "info": "What item of clothing was named after its Scottish inventor?",
        "Answer": "A Mackintosh"
      },
      {
        "question": "6",
        "info": "What kind of weapon is a falchion?",
        "Answer": "A sword"
      },
      {
        "question": "7",
        "info": "Which word goes before vest, beans and quartet?",
        "Answer": "String"
      },
      {
        "question": "8",
        "info": "What is another word for lexicon?",
        "Answer": "Dictionary"
      },
      {
        "question": "9",
        "info": "Name the seventh planet from the sun.",
        "Answer": "Uranus"
      },
      {
        "question": "10",
        "info": "Who invented the rabies vaccination?",
        "Answer": "Uranus"
      }
    ],
    "trueOrFalseQuestions": [
      {
        "question": "11",
        "info": "True or false, Bill gates invented Apple",
        "Answer": "False"
      },
      {
        "question": "12",
        "info": "True or false, Steve Jobs invented Apple",
        "Answer": "True"
      },
      {
        "question": "13",
        "info": "Barrack Obama was the 3rd president",
        "Answer": "False"
      },
      {
        "question": "14",
        "info": "Will Arnett plays Gob in Arrested Development",
        "Answer": "True"
      },
      {
        "question": "15",
        "info": "Linus Torvalds is the maintainer of Linux",
        "Answer": "True"
      }
    ],
    "multipleChoiceQuestionsOneAnswer": [
      {
        "question": "16",
        "info": "What year did the Paris Commune rise up?",
        "options": [
          "1870",
          "1871",
          "1872",
          "1873"
        ],
        "Answer": "1871"
      },
      {
        "question": "17",
        "info": "What year did the Soviet Union fall?",
        "options": [
          "1989",
          "1990",
          "1991",
          "1992"
        ],
        "Answer": "1991"
      },
      {
        "question": "18",
        "info": "What year did Civ 5 release?",
        "options": [
          "2007",
          "2008",
          "2009",
          "2010"
        ],
        "Answer": "2010"
      },
      {
        "question": "19",
        "info": "Which band is the best?",
        "options": [
          "Grateful Dead",
          "Wham!",
          "Marky Mark and the Funky Bunch",
          "Miami Sound Machine"
        ],
        "Answer": "Grateful Dead"
      },
      {
        "question": "20",
        "info": "Which Programming Language exists",
        "options": [
          "LISP",
          "Burnout Paradise!",
          "Gamethyon",
          "Teascript "
        ],
        "Answer": "LISP"
      }
    ]
  }
}
